Charles R. Martin Photographs, 1945-2011 AIS.2012.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, 1945-1998; II.
  - 35mm Negatives, 1.
    - 1985
      - United Way- Boys Club, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 28)
      - United Way- Vintage/ Brashear, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 29)
      - United Way- Vintage, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 30)
      - United Way- Speech Hearing and Deaf Services, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 31)
      - United Way, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 33)
      - United Way- Health – O – Rama, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 34)
      - United Way- Cerebral Palsy, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 35, 40)
      - United Way- Hill House/ Vintage, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 36)
      - United Way- Holy Family, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 37)
      - United Way- Salvation Army, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 39, 46)
      - United Way- Vocational Rehabilitation Center/ Cerebral Palsy/ Speech and Hearing, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 42)
      - United Way- Hill House, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 43)
      - Ocracoke, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 47)
      - Golden Quill Awards, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 48-50)
      - Contax 1.5, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 57)
      - Personal- Leica Chrome III, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 58)
      - United Way- Helen & Betty Brady – Cerebral Palsy, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 59)
      - United Way- Doug Lisiecki Hemophiliac, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 60)
      - Personal- M-4- Start of Foot Race, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - United Way, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 2-4)
      - Bike Race, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 5-10)
      - Crete- Sumerian Gorge, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Ocracoke- Kitty & Gary, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 12-14)
      - Personal- Leica III, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Personal- Lilypad, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Kuigua Tri, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Hot Harry's Picture, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 19-20)
      - United Way- Report Lunch, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 21-22)
      - Bio-Energetiks, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 23-24, 30-31)
      - Touchstone Craft Center, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Sweetwater- Italian Cabaret Night, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Personal- M-2 1.8 35mm, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - Big Dude in Kurt's Sonnet (?), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 28)
      - Hot Harry's Running Club, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 29)
      - Personal- Kokolis Copies, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 32)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 33)
      - United Way- Parade, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 34-35)
      - United Way, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 36)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Thanksgiving, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 37-38)
      - Ron Niuldeukauep, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 39)
      - Personal- Christmas '85 & Moe's 1st Real Estate Venture, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - 1986
      Subjects include United Way; Pittsburgh Blind Association; Greece; Bio-Energetiks; Golden Quill Awards; Touchstone; St. Barnabas; McBeth. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and camera test photographs.
      - Personal- Contax IIA, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 41)
      - United Way- Awards– William Penn, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 42)
      - Personal- Leica IIIA Red Eye, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 43)
      - Personal- Camera Test, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 44)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association- Person of Vision Lunch, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 45-46)
      - St. Barnabas- Patients & Family Dining Room, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 47)
      - St. Barnabas- Med Center, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 48)
      - Personal- Warsaw Senior English Class & Pittsburgh Point, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 49)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 50-52)
      - McBeth Copies, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 53)
      - St. Barnabas- Special Dinner- Patients & Family, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 54)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Warrendale – Dr. Wyielko w/ Client, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 55)
      - McBeth- Copies from Slides, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 56)
      - Personal-, Snow, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 57)
      - United Way- Illiteracy Task Force Meeting, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 58-59)
      - Bio-Energetiks, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 60-63, 67-68)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Beaver Office, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 64)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Map Office, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 65-66)
      - Dale Neuman w/ Congressman Doug Walgren, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 69-70)
      - Golden Quill Awards, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
      - Misc. & Hands Across America, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Bio-Energetiks, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Greece '86, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 6-19)
      - Gary Smith- PR Pix, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Dale Neuman- B&W Copies of Slides, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - United Way- Labor Day Parade United Way Float, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 23-26)
      - Touchstone, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 27-28)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Map, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Map & New Cranberry Office Planning, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 30)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Warrendale, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 31-32)
      - Personal- M2 test, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 33)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Butler Office, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - Personal- XA Test, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 35)
      - Old Sewickley Post Office, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 36)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Beaver, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 37)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Beaver- Map, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 38)
      - D.C. & Spanish Students at Chi-Chi's, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 39)
      - Om 4 Test, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 40)
      - Gary Smith & Family, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 41-42)
      - Neil Fischer- B/W Slide copies, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - 1987
      Subjects include Bidwell Jazz; Sweetwater Art Center; Bio-Energetiks; St. Francis Executive Health club; Buhl Science Center; Golden Quill; St. Barnabas; Dargate Gallery; United Way. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and camera test photos.
      - United Way- General Meeting- Vista Hotel, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 44-45)
      - St. Barnabas- Bill Rapp, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 46)
      - Personal, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 47, 49, 52, 66-67)
      - Personal- Contax IIA, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 48)
      - Dargate Gallery, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 50, 52)
      - St. Barnabas, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 53-54)
      - St. Barnabas- South African Visitors, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 55-56)
      - St. Barnabas Auxiliary Officer Installation, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 57)
      - Sweetwater Reception, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 58)
      - Golden Quill Awards, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 59-63)
      - Red Valve Shoot, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 64)
      - Bio-Energetics, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 65)
      - St. Francis Health Club, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 68-70)
      - St. Francis Health Club- Teen Group, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
      - Personal- Nova Scotia, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Buhl, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5-12)
      - St. Francis Executive Health Club, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Personal- XA a/ Mamiya, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Personal- Test, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 15-16)
      - Personal- XA Misc.- Ohio Bike R & Sweetwater Opening, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Cranberry, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 18-19)
      - Sweetwater- Acrylics Class (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Carson Group- Chris Steak House (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Sweetwater- Jewelry Class (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - Trolley Model- Al Saul & Gabe Kassob (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Personal- Vermont '87 (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Personal- M2 (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - Sweetwater Opera Café (Box 65, Folder 26)
      - Sweetwater (Box 65, Folder 27-29, 34)
      - Personal- Gulls (Box 65, Folder 30)
      - Jones & Laughlin– Midland, PA (Box 65, Folder 31)
      - Jones & Laughlin and Truck Depot (Box 65, Folder 32)
      - Personal- M4-2, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 33)
      - Bidwell Jazz Concert, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 35-37, 39-41)
      - Personal- III b –Test, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - 1988
      Subjects include Sweetwater Art Center; Generations Together; Presents for Patients; Buhl Science Awards. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Tomoka Work, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 42)
      - Bike Ride with Metzger, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 43)
      - Cottage, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 44)
      - Symphony & Greece Dancers, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 45)
      - Personal, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 46)
      - XA – Donegal- Stuck on 2.8, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 47, 49)
      - Re-enactors, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 48)
      - Personal- III B Test, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 50)
      - Personal- Jewelry Pix, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 51)
      - Personal- M2 1.4 Lux, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 52)
      - B/W Slide Copies- Paris & Rome, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 53)
      - Buhl Science Awards, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 54-55)
      - Buhl Science Awards, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Personal- M4-2, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Personal- Dave H. at J.D., 1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Generations Together- Banquet, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Hartwood Acres Concert, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Personal- Pooch, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Presents for Patients, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 7-8)
      - Personal- 200mm 2.8 & 3.5 mm 2.8 Test, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Personal- XA w/ T max Test, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Personal- IIIb, f2 Summar, t3.5 Elmar, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Island- Color, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 12-13)
      - Personal- M4-2, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Personal- Fallingwater, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Sweetwater- Opera Cabaret, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Generations Together, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 17-22)
      - Personal- 90mm Elmar Test, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Carson Group Shots, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 24-25)
      - Sweetwater, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 27-28, 30)
      - Personal- Red Leica III w/ Summar, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - 1989
      Subjects include PCC; St. Barnabas; Sweetwater Art Center; Lucy Jones; and various scenic views. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Night Shots of Pittsburgh and Allegheny Center, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - Personal- Shots of Pittsburgh and Misc., 1989 (Box 66, Folder 32)
      - Personal- Grey IIIc, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 33)
      - Personal- M4-2 - 1.4 Lux, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 34)
      - Personal- M4-2 35 mm 1.4 Lux, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - Personal- M4-2 - Summeron 50 vs Summalux 50 Test, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - International Images, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 37-38)
      - P.C.C.- Copies of Slides for PR Release, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 39)
      - St. Barnabas, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 40)
      - Sweetwater- Frank Mason Reception and Lecture, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 41)
      - Lucy Jones, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 42-45)
      - P.C.C- Mrs. Casey visit/ July 4th- Hares, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 46)
      - P.C.C. & Ohiopyle, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 47)
      - Personal- Touchstone, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 48)
      - Personal- XA, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 49-51)
      - Personal- M4, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 52)
      - Personal- XA Test Sweetwater Class, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 53)
      - Personal- Ocracoke- 90 mm 2.8 Leica Test, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 54)
      - Personal, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - 1990
      Subjects include Nature Shots; Touchstone; Vocational Rehabilitation Center; Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- 50 mm Summecron coll. F2 Test, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 56)
      - Lisa Parkett Art Works, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 57)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 58)
      - Touchstone- Slide Copies, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 59)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 60-71)
      - Personal- Test, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 72)
      - Personal, 73, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 73)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Easter, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 74-77)
      - Personal- Camera Test, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 78)
      - International Images, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 79)
      - Personal- Red Leica III- Laurel Highlands, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 80)
      - Personal- Red Leica III, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Touchstone- Renata Sawyer, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Personal- Touchstone & Laurel Highlands area, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Touchstone, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Pittsburgh History & Landmarks Foundation, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 5-9)
      - Personal- Touchstone, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Personal- Rolex for Insurance, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Personal- 1st of Series 1.8 Canon, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 12-14)
      - Personal- Ocracoke- Thanksgiving, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Schnaubelt Sports, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Personal- Ocracoke- Uncle Ben, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Personal- Charlie Byrd at Sweetwater, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Personal- 90mm Leite 2.8 Lens Test, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Personal, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 20, 27)
      - Touchstone- Slide Copies for 1991 Catalog, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - 1991
      Subjects include Cabot Oil & Gas; Industrial Scientific; Postal Metro Union; Vocational Rehab Center; Generations Together; Touchstone; McBeth. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Postal Metro Union- Roll I, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Postal Metro Union- Roll II, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Touchstone- Slide Copies for Brochure, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Personal- Test, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Personal- M4, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Generations Together, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Personal- IIIA Summitar, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Personal- Elmar/Summar/Summitar Test, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 31-33)
      - Personal- Treesdale F, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - Personal- IIIA, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - McBeth, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Hardy Nickerson, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 37-41)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 42)
      - Postal Metro Union, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 43-44)
      - Personal- Pittsburgh Bike Race, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 45)
      - Industrial Scientific- (Al Saul), 1991 (Box 67, Folder 46-50)
      - Personal- Gravesite, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 51)
      - Personal- Cumberland RR Trip, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 52-53)
      - Personal- Contax 167 w/ 2.8-8.5, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 54-55, 57)
      - Personal- Contax 167, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 56)
      - Personal- B&W Copies, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 58)
      - Personal- M4-2 Test after Overhaul, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 59)
      - Personal- M4-2- Bidwell Center Jazz, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 60)
      - Personal- 167 w/283, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 61)
      - McBeth- Bidwell, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 62-63)
      - Cabot Oil & Gas- John Cabot Visit, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 64-66)
      - Personal- Contax IIA 1.5, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 67)
      - Personal- Elmar 3.5 mm Test, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 68)
      - Personal- IIIA Elmar 35 & 90, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 69)
      - N. Chambers, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 70)
      - Personal, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 71)
      - Personal- Ocracoke & Condo, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 72)
    - 1992
      Subjects include Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Montour Trail Council; Vocational Rehab Center; Ketcham Inc.; Chatham College; Health & Welfare Association; Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); Bercer & Assocation Co.; United Fund; Community Services of Pennsylvania; Kellogg Media Group. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Vermont Bike Trip, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 73)
      - Personal- Chas. Thomas, Jeff Martin, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 74)
      - Italian Oven, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 75-77)
      - Personal- Chas. T. J. Martin, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 78)
      - Geo. Skgling, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 79)
      - Cap-Gemini at Ketchum Inc., 1992 (Box 67, Folder 80)
      - Cap-Gemini at Ketchum Inc., 1992 (Box 68, Folder 1-7)
      - Personal- C.T J. Martin, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Personal- Bill Metzger & Dog "Valentine", 1992 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Allstate Linens- Shower Curtain, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Personal- Touchstone, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
      - Personal, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Chuck Martin – Cranberry Show Opening, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 14-15)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 16-18)
      - Personal- Contax, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Leica M4-2, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Personal- Canon Test, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Personal- Contax- Flash Test, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Larry Cohen, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Montour Trail Council Meeting, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - 1993
      Subjects include Touchstone; Generations Together Airport Show; Enterprise Foundation; Ocracoke Island, North Carolina; Matthews International. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Icy Tree, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Hole to Infinity, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Bernice & Elizab, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - Personal- Canon, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 31, 35)
      - N.C. Hike, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 29-30)
      - Personal- Copies, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - Personal- OM 2 - Charlie, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Matthews International, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - Personal- Canon AEZ Test, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 37-38, 40)
      - Personal, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 39, 56-59, 62)
      - Ocracoke- Easter, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 41)
      - Enterprise Foundation, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 42-43)
      - Generations Together, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 44)
      - Personal- IIb Test, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 45)
      - Personal- Older IIIB, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 46)
      - Personal- New IIIB, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 47)
      - Touchstone, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 48-49)
      - Generations Together- Airport Show, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 50)
      - Generations Together- Seminar, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 51-53)
      - Personal- IIIb (late), 1992 (Box 68, Folder 54)
      - Personal- M4-2, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 55)
      - Personal- Leica Sal's Pics, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 60)
      - Penn Dot- Rt 22-30 & 60 Intersection Near Robinson Town Center, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 61)
      - Personal- Canon IIF, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 63)
      - Personal- Canon IIF w/ 1.8 test, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 64)
      - Personal- Fed Lens Test, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 65)
      - Personal- Elan, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 66)
      - Personal- M4-2 Mr. Meter P3200 Film, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 67)
      - Personal- Snow, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 68)
      - Personal- Bradford Woods Major Bldg ("skyline"), 1993 (Box 68, Folder 69)
      - Ocracoke- Canon, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 70)
      - Ocracoke- Fish House & Old Trees, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 71)
      - Ocracoke- Fish House, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 72)
      - Ocracoke- Jam Session, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 73)
      - Personal- IIIA, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 74)
      - Personal- Contax II-1.5, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 75)
    - 1994
      Subjects include Generations Together and Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Leica IIIA, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 76)
      - Personal- Snow & Bradford Woods, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 77)
      - Personal- III Summar w/ Light Yellow Filter, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 78)
      - Personal- Garage Wall- Lincoln Insurance Claim, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 79)
      - Personal- Hockey Game, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 80)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Easter, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
      - Generations Together, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 3-7)
      - Personal & St. Barnabas- Kris Long – WPXI Copy, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Personal- Turtle & Sharks, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Personal- Delta Wall, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Personal- Test, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 11-13)
      - Personal- Canon, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Personal- Hare's – July 4th, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Charlie & Bernice- Sept. 1994 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Personal- 100-300 Test Canon, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Personal- Nikon, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Personal- S-2 Test, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 18, 20)
      - S-2- Ocracoke, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Delta Film- Underdeveloped, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - 1995
      This year contains Martin's personal images.
      - Personal- Sal's I.D. Picture, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Personal- Shoot at Warhol Museum w/ Ed Dellis, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Personal- Nikon F Test, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Personal- Nikon 52 Test, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Personal- III G, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Personal- FE Test, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 27, 29)
      - Personal, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Personal- FE w/ 24-70 Tamron Zoom Test, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Personal- New FE 100-24-70 & 20 Test, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Personal- Summar - Elmar - Summitar, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - 1996
      Subjects include Action Housing; Generations Together; Pittsburgh Sports Festival; and public relations photographs.
      - Personal- Retina Focus Check, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - Personal- Canon w/ Elmar, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - Personal- IIIc w/ctd Summatar & 3.5 elmar, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Personal- IIIc Elmar, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 36)
      - Personal- III C Summer – Glade – Summatar, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 37)
      - FE- Velcro Bounce test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 38)
      - Action Housing, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 39-40, 45-67)
      - Generations Together & Flash Tests, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 41, 72)
      - R.R. Stuff w/ Bill M & Flash Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 42)
      - Pittsburgh Sports & Festival News Conference, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 43-44)
      - Pittsburgh Sports Festival- Greg Le Monde, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 68-69)
      - Personal- Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 70)
      - Personal- EM fz 35, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 71)
      - Personal- Larry Shaftar's (?) Tree Crew & McConnell's Null, Nikon EM Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 73)
      - Personal- Canon Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 74)
      - Personal- IIIG w/ CTD Summitar, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 75)
      - Leica Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 76)
      - Personal- FE Test, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 77)
    - 1997
      Subjects include Action Housing; St. Barnabas; Ocracoke Island, North Carolina. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and camera test photos.
      - Martin- Workshop Ocracoke, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 1-2, 5)
      - III B- Late Summar, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - FE, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Personal- IIIb w/ 3.5 Elmar, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Personal- III C & Canon 50/1.8, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - B. Falls Bridge & Bradford Woods Reserve – March Snow, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - St. Barnabas- Val. Woods, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 9-10)
      - Personal- CTD Summar Test, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Personal- M6 – 1.4 35, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Action Housing- Ed Schwaatz & William Coleman, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Personal- Jones Mill Cottage, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 14, 23-24)
      - S-2 Nikon w/f2.5 35 mm, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Personal- Canon VT Test, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Personal & St. Barnabas Copy Job- Rodey Rivers, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Personal- Canon 7 Test, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Personal- IIIA CTD. Summar, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 19, 21)
      - Personal- IIIA w CTD Summar, 3.5 mm elmar, 9 cm Elmar, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Personal- M6 1.4 35mm asph., 1997 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Personal- Summar & Canon, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Personal- Delta 400, Pike Run Hiks, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Personal- FE & 283 Flash Test, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Personal- HP 5, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - 1998